<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<!DOCTYPE packagegui SYSTEM "../schema/packages.dtd">
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../xsl/package.xsl"?>
<packagegui>
	<copyright>
	<![CDATA[
/*
 * snort.xml
 *
 * part of pfSense (https://www.pfsense.org)
 * Copyright (c) 2015 Rubicon Communications, LLC (Netgate)
 * Copyright (c) 2009-2010 Robert Zelaya
 * Copyright (c) 2013-2016 Bill Meeks
 * All rights reserved.
 *
 * Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
 * you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
 * You may obtain a copy of the License at
 *
 * http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
 *
 * Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
 * distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
 * WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
 * See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
 * limitations under the License.
 */
/* $Id$ */
/* ====================================================================================== */
/*
	snort.xml
	part of pfSense (https://www.pfSense.org/)
	Copyright (C) 2009-2010 Robert Zelaya
	Copyright (C) 2013-2015 Bill Meeks
	All rights reserved.
*/
/* ====================================================================================== */
/*
	Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
	modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:


	1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice,
	   this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.

	2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
	   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the
	   documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.


	THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED ``AS IS'' AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES,
	INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY
	AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
	AUTHOR BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY,
	OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF
	SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS
	INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN
	CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE)
	ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE
	POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
*/
/* ====================================================================================== */
	]]>
	</copyright>
	<description>Snort IDS/IPS Package</description>
	<name>Snort</name>
	<version>%%PKGVERSION%%</version>
	<title>Services: Snort IDS</title>
	<include_file>/usr/local/pkg/snort/snort.inc</include_file>
	<menu>
		<name>Snort</name>
		<tooltiptext>Set up snort specific settings</tooltiptext>
		<section>Services</section>
		<url>/snort/snort_interfaces.php</url>
	</menu>
	<service>
		<name>snort</name>
		<rcfile>snort.sh</rcfile>
		<executable>snort</executable>
		<description>Snort IDS/IPS Daemon</description>
	</service>
	<tabs>
	</tabs>
	<fields>
	</fields>
	<custom_php_resync_config_command>
		<![CDATA[
		sync_snort_package_config();
		]]>
	</custom_php_resync_config_command>
	<custom_php_install_command>
		<![CDATA[
		include_once("/usr/local/pkg/snort/snort_post_install.php");
		]]>
	</custom_php_install_command>
	<custom_php_pre_deinstall_command>
		<![CDATA[
		include_once("/usr/local/pkg/snort/snort_uninstall.php");
		]]>
	</custom_php_pre_deinstall_command>
</packagegui>
